VITALII PROSKURA



OBJECTIVE

JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

Contact details **Tel.:** +380965067381

Email: vitalii.proskura@gmail.com

Skype: a255912924 LinkedIn: Vitalii Proskura GitHub: diomedtedid

Current location Ready for relocate

LANGUAGELevelEnglishUpper intermediateRussianNativeUkrainianNative

SUMMARY

I have experience and knowledge with IT and related technologies (I have a computer since 1988, Installation and support of computer networks, Microcontrollers, Studding Java since 2014, etc.)

Great experience in communication and interaction with IT staff.

Good speaking English and great experience in communications with people from different countries and cultures.

TECHNICAL SKILLS				
Languages:	JavaSE (Core , JDBC, IO, Reflection, Network)			
	J2EE (Servlet, JPA, JSP, JMS);			
Frameworks	Spring (IoC, MVC, Security)			
	Hibernate			
	JUnit, Mockito			
DB:	MySQL	SQLite	H2	
IDE:	Intellij Idea			
Others:	Arduino, Raspberry Pi, ESPxx			
	HTML/CSS, JavaScript			
	Linux (Debian / Ubuntu)			
	Tomcat			

SOFT SKILLS

Devil's calm, Ability to professionally learn, Can work in extreme conditions (25/8, Bloody management, etc.), Can find common ground with any person and team, Ability to learn new languages

Scrum

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION	Specialization	Duration	Year of graduation/City/ Country
GoIT	Java EE	8 months	September 2017, Kiev
EDUCATION			
Dniepropetrovs State	General and Social	5 years	2006, Master's degree, Dnipro
University. Ukraine	Psychology	•	, , , ,

WORK EXPERIENCE	
Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Responsibilities	Senior Dolphin Assisted Therapist/Administrator Dolphinariums network "Nemo" www.therapynemo.com 30.11.2010- now / Odessa/Kyiv Ukraine - Experience of work with people from many countries - Organizational assistance in opening new departments (different countries) - Recruitment and adaptation of new staff from different countries;
Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Responsibilities	Statistic researches and Data analysis Freelance 2005 – now / Ukraine - Statistical calculations Calculation of student diplomas Organization and calculations of sociological research Mathematical calibration of psychological tests.
Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Responsibilities	Waiter Caviar house and Pruner, Dubai www.caviarhouse-prunier.com 1.08.2014-04.06.2015 / Dubai, UAE - Work with costumers in Dubai International Airport
Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Responsibilities	Project manager ECF educational company 1.12.2007 – 10.12.2008 / Dnipro city, Ukraine - Project management of alternative educational programs.
Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Responsibilities	HR manager Archer Software IT company www.archer-soft.com 21.06.2006 – 30.11.2007 / Dnipro city, Ukraine - The search, the selection and the adaptation of the operating staff (IT) - The monitoring of the personnel's motivation and the dynamic processes in the working groups; - The organization of the corporative arrangements (seminars, parties); - The registration of leaves of absence and sick leaves; - The documentation-keeping (employment-dismissal, elaboration of the projects)

Job title Company's name Period / City / Country Teacher, Psychologist N.93 High School 01.09.2005 – 25.05.2006 / Dnipro city, Ukraine